http://www.yourtickettowork.com/privacy-policy.html

Toggle navigation
Social Security AdministrationSocial Security Work SiteFor BeneficiariesFor Service ProvidersBigger TextSmaller Text
Toggle navigation
AboutEmployment NetworksState VR AgenciesProgram OperationsTraining and EventsResourcesContact Us
TTW
Privacy PolicyWhat information do we collect?We collect information from you when you fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To personalize your experience — Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.To improve our website — We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.To improve customer service — Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.To send periodic emails — The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.Note: If you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails at any time, contact the EN/VR Helpline at 866-949-3687 or at ENOperations@yourtickettowork.ssa.gov.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.Do we use cookies?Yes — Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and interactions so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA. We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section, which establishes the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at https://yourtickettowork.ssa.gov/.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our website's privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on 10/4/2018.Contacting UsIf you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below:Website: https://yourtickettowork.ssa.govMailing Address:Ticket to Work Program  P.O. Box 1433  Alexandria, VA 22313-1433  USA Email: ENOperations@yourtickettowork.ssa.govPhone: 866-949-3687
